<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<feed xmlns='http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom' xmlns:blogger='http://schemas.google.com/blogger/2018'>
  <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-5478531773743484939</id>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-5478531773743484939.post-1931595965160968505</id>
    <blogger:type>POST</blogger:type>
    <blogger:status>LIVE</blogger:status>
    <author>
      <name>that one guy</name>
      <blogger:type>BLOGGER</blogger:type>
    </author>
    <title>what is the difference between science and religion?</title>
    <content type='html'>Both science and religion are stories (&lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Meme"&gt;memes&lt;/a&gt;) useful in explaining reality. There are distinct survival advantages to having a story -- it allows for prediction of cause and effect.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;The difference from religion is that science makes physically quantifiable measurements to form the story. As a result, there is one coherent story. Though partial (an incomplete set of knowledge), there is a clear &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Scientific_method"&gt;method&lt;/a&gt; for adding to the knowledge.</content>
    <blogger:created>2012-10-26T23:17:14.703Z</blogger:created>
    <published>2012-10-26T23:20:00.001Z</published>
    <updated>2012-10-26T23:20:10.523Z</updated>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-5478531773743484939.post-2108597417754297459</id>
    <blogger:type>POST</blogger:type>
    <blogger:status>LIVE</blogger:status>
    <author>
      <name>that one guy</name>
      <blogger:type>BLOGGER</blogger:type>
    </author>
    <title>open and closed systems of thinking</title>
    <content type='html'>&lt;i&gt;definition&lt;/i&gt;: an "open system of knowledge" is set of knowledge in which there exist questions which are quantifiably answerable but which have not yet been. There are known unknowns.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;i&gt;claim&lt;/i&gt;: science is an open system of knowledge. Whether due to lack of funding or lack of capable scientists, not all questions are answered. This may result in feelings of powerlessness.&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;i&gt;definition&lt;/i&gt;: a "closed system of knowledge" is a set of knowledge in which all questions are answerable.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;i&gt;claim&lt;/i&gt;: religion is a closed system of knowledge. All questions can be answered with generic answers such as "it is the will of God" or "it is part of God's plan." [These make no quantifiably testable predictions.] The result of the ability to answer all questions is a feeling of comfort -- someone is in charge of the seemingly crazy events. However, there can be a corresponding decrease in curiosity in seeking knowledge. Any action can be justified using the above generic answers. The ability to question the validity of these answers is also closed.&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
</content>
    <blogger:created>2012-10-26T23:01:39.784Z</blogger:created>
    <published>2012-10-26T23:11:00.001Z</published>
    <updated>2017-02-04T14:46:16.223Z</updated>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-5478531773743484939.post-2593875367293460246</id>
    <blogger:type>POST</blogger:type>
    <blogger:status>LIVE</blogger:status>
    <author>
      <name>that one guy</name>
      <blogger:type>BLOGGER</blogger:type>
    </author>
    <title>where I am now</title>
    <content type='html'>I occasionally run across &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Atheism"&gt;atheists&lt;/a&gt; debating religious people. I feel sorry for the atheists, since they are invariably wasting their time. If religious people were logical, a debate might be meaningful. Often the atheist feels they have logic on their side, so they must be able to convince the religious person.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
The religious person built their perspective on faith -- making decisions without evidence or even&amp;nbsp;in spite&amp;nbsp;of conflicting evidence. The religious perspective is not logical, thus logical arguments don't result in agreement with the&amp;nbsp;atheist.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
The root of lack of progress in any conversation can be traced to a problem with definitions. Either two parties don't agree on a definition, or there isn't a definition for the term. In either case, stop any talk until this lack of definitions or disagreement on definitions is resolved. &amp;nbsp;A person new to &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ignosticism"&gt;ignosticism&lt;/a&gt; may have difficulty with implementing this to sufficient detail.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
When I say the word "&lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Capacitor"&gt;capacitor&lt;/a&gt;," I am referring to a physical device with measurable properties. In this case a capacitor stores energy in an electric field (which can be physically quantified). A &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Chicken"&gt;chicken&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;(also physically&amp;nbsp;measurable)&amp;nbsp; is very difficult to confuse with a capacitor. We use words to describe physical objects we are thinking about. How can we use words for more (apparently) abstract concepts like "freedom" and "happy"?&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
It turns out "&lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Happiness"&gt;happiness&lt;/a&gt;" can &lt;a href="http://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0925492797000632"&gt;be measured&lt;/a&gt; by a &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Functional_magnetic_resonance_imaging"&gt;functional MRIs&lt;/a&gt;, as can most feelings (depression, anger). On the other hand, the words like "&lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Freedom"&gt;freedom&lt;/a&gt;" are subjective because they lack any physical object or commonly-agreed upon measurement to make. What we &lt;i&gt;can&lt;/i&gt; talk about &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Objectivity_(philosophy)"&gt;objectively&lt;/a&gt; are the physical actions individuals take under the heading of freedom.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;i&gt;Summary&lt;/i&gt;: &lt;br /&gt;
If a person cannot define the terms they are using in a physically-quantifiably meaningful way, then any argument made using those terms is unmeasurable. If a statement is not measurable, then there is no way to test its validity.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;</content>
    <blogger:created>2012-10-26T22:30:59.064Z</blogger:created>
    <published>2012-10-26T23:01:00Z</published>
    <updated>2017-02-04T14:45:47.827Z</updated>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-5478531773743484939.post-7349884638515314392</id>
    <blogger:type>POST</blogger:type>
    <blogger:status>LIVE</blogger:status>
    <author>
      <name>that one guy</name>
      <blogger:type>BLOGGER</blogger:type>
    </author>
    <title>logically dealing with illogic</title>
    <content type='html'>&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;i&gt;claim&lt;/i&gt;: Religion is illogical; science is logical.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;i&gt;Question&lt;/i&gt;: Can a logical thought system (science) be used to describe the illogic of religion?&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;i&gt;Answer&lt;/i&gt;:&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Efficacy_of_prayer"&gt;Yes&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
A test of illogical systems of thought is their multiplicity. Any illogical system is equally useless. &amp;nbsp;[Some have more attractive memetic qualities.] &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Hindu"&gt;Hindus&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Christian"&gt;Christians&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Buddhism"&gt;Buddhists&lt;/a&gt; have divergent views on cause and effect. [Again, commonality arises due to memetic survival.]&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
In contrast, there is one &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Scientific_method"&gt;scientific method&lt;/a&gt;. Many disciplines exist (geology, physics, chemistry) but they apply the same method.&lt;/div&gt;
</content>
    <blogger:created>2012-10-26T23:11:45.664Z</blogger:created>
    <published>2012-10-26T23:16:00.002Z</published>
    <updated>2017-02-04T14:46:34.114Z</updated>
  </entry>
</feed>