<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<feed xmlns='http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom' xmlns:blogger='http://schemas.google.com/blogger/2018'>
  <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-5921014943647686064</id>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-5921014943647686064.post-1832727283179870969</id>
    <blogger:type>POST</blogger:type>
    <blogger:status>LIVE</blogger:status>
    <author>
      <name>that one guy</name>
      <blogger:type>BLOGGER</blogger:type>
    </author>
    <title>sailing in Greece, September 2016</title>
    <content type='html'>Sailed the Mediterranean with 5 other people&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;i&gt;Tuesday September 27&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
Woke up in Athens in the Backpackers hostel at 2:25am. My alarm was loud enough to wake me from 10' away with earplugs, so I'm confident the other 5 people were awakened.&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
Stumbled upon the x95 bus in Syntagma square a minute before it departed at 2:50am&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
I had checked in online Monday. This was useful, as I wasn't able to get a paper ticket from the self checkin kiosk.&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
Swiss airlines is great - breakfast was a yummy egg, cheese, and tomato quiche with orange juice. A flight attendant accidentally give me a second serving, which I happily ate.&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
Most of the flight to Zurich was spent reading a book I picked up in the hostel.&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;i&gt;Monday, September 26&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
Woke around 7:30am in Fira backpackers hostel. Showered, walked to a bakery for a pastry after eating a packet of oatmeal.&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
Caught 11:30am &amp;nbsp;bus to the port for €2.40, a 25 minute ride&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
The first boat to arrive was Champion Jet 2, 35 minutes late. I got on and was told that I should wait for the next boat (my ticket was for 13:10). The boat I got on was much smaller. I'm confined to the bottom floor and there is no outside access. Smaller boat means more shaking and rolling.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
Food today:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
Oatmeal packet&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
Spinach pastry&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
Nut bar&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
Bag of mixed nuts and raisins&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
Baklava and milk&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;i&gt;Sunday, &amp;nbsp;September 25&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
Woke around 8am in Fira backpackers hostel&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
Talked to an Asian girl over breakfast of 3 oatmeal packets. Kasin is a graphic design undergrad from Montreal, Canada. Baptist who goes to raves. Came to Athens via a dating website&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
Hung out with Kasin until noon&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
€2.40 bus and 45 minutes to Perissa beach&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
€5 umbrella fee. Meditated and peed in the ocean.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
Bus back to Fira around 5:45pm&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
Read a book, The Magician of Lhasa. Very good - I finished the 250+ pages around 12:45am. To sleep after 1am&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;i&gt;Saturday Sept 24&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
Woke in Zea marina, Athens, to my alarm at 5:38am. Although it was quiet overnight, the smell of sewage was strong and interfered with my sleep.&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
Found Frank waiting at the taxi at 5:56am. Drove to the ferry terminal. Cost was €10 because Frank had pre-arranged the taxi, whereas Friday it had cost €3.5 and €4 when we caught Taxis on the street.&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
"Champion Jet 2" costs €43.70 to Santorini and departed at 7am. It's about half full, so I was able to find a nice seat by the window with an outlet for charging my phone.&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
Caught the sunrise as we departed Athens.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
Later lost my sunglasses in the wind as we passed the island of Kea&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
Arrived in Mikonos at 10:10am, departed 10:20&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
37°27'49.9"N 25°19'28.1"E&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
http://maps.google.com/?q=37.463861,25.324475&amp;amp;hl=en&amp;amp;gl=us&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
Next to Naxos. Arrived 11:05, departed 11&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
http://maps.google.com/?q=37.105913,25.372589&amp;amp;hl=en&amp;amp;gl=us&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
Arrived santorini at 12:45&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
Bus to Fira town center bus station for €2.70&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
Walked to the nearest hostel&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
€16&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
Bus to Oia, €1.80. Talked with a girl spending a semester in Italy.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
Wandering the town, there are plenty of tourists.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
The girls seem to be competing with the environment for most beautiful with the effort made very clear&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
Walked down the 200+ steps in Oia to the water. Wandered to a swim spot (Amoudi Bay) and went for a swim.&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
Back up the steps to the Byzantine Castle Ruins&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
http://maps.google.com/?cid=14861198028050229381&amp;amp;hl=en&amp;amp;gl=us&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
Waited 1.5 hours for the sunset at 7:12. I meditated and watched people to pass the time.&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
Caught the bus at 8pm back to Fira.&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
In bed around 10pm&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
Nice overlook, secluded:&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
https://goo.gl/maps/QFR7xcjMbYE2&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
Bus station&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
https://goo.gl/maps/VdtFRFSfeWK2&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;i&gt;Friday September 23&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
Woke in Poros. No water, a broken head, and everyone looking forward to returning to the base in Athens&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
Motored, then sailed for 30 minutes, then motored.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
Arrived at Zea marina around 3:30pm&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
Water pump was replaced. Sandy did the boat debriefing.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
"No tomorrow party" on Sheri's boat at 5pm. Lots of snacks. Frank and I went to the prieus port to buy ferry tickets but the office was closed.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
Sandy, Pat, Debora, Teresa, and I went to the nearby restaurant where Sandy ordered too much food and I helped eat some.&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
I went to be around 10:30pm. Sandy woke me up at 11:45 to help her and John get to the taxi. I went back to sleep quickly&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;i&gt;Thursday September 22&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
Woke in Mandraki bay around 7am&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
https://goo.gl/maps/VfzKXNwCNi92&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
Very peaceful and calm environment.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
I took pat and Debra into shore with the dingy. They walked to Hydra and took a water taxi back to the boat&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
Cast off around 10am&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
Motored towards Poros due to weather forecast for thunderstorms&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
Sailed for a while&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
Arrived in Poros around noon (13 nautical miles)&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
Ate lunch on the boat. I ate too much and was dehydrated, so I took a nap while everyone else wandered.&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
Where we docked there was a house under active construction. There were about 10 men, ages 30 to 60, loafing around doing minimal actions. It didn't look like an American work site.&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
Dinner at Apagio Taverna&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;i&gt;Wednesday September 21&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
Woke in Skindos bay, island of Dokos. Slept well - ear plugs were well seated and there was no noise. Made hash browns and scrambled eggs. Went swimming. &amp;nbsp;Departed 11am&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
Motored to Mandraki bay. Set a Bohemian mooring with two stern lines. We snacked. A squall blew past and missed us.&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
I set a third line to shore from the midship cleat. Used the dinghy to bring Sandy, John, and Pat to shore. John, Sandy, and I walked to Hydra for provisions. We took a water taxi back to the boat.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
I took the dinghy to the other two boats. I picked up more olive oil from Sheri.&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
Pat made pasta for supper.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;i&gt;Tuesday September 20&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
Woke in Plaka. I had been up for a while. Overnight the wind was gusty - the waves sounded like arrhythmic bongos against the hulls.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
At 7am I stretched, pooped, then swam. The ocean was not cold and is very clear with a slight aqua tint. I used the warm shower on the beach, then went back to the boat for a bit more yoga.&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
At 9am we took Taxis to Monastery of Elona&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
The road is twisty and narrow. A monk and nun, both old, were present. The Munk guided us around.&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
Motored out of Plaka. Sailed for 30 minutes.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
Bohemian Moore in skindos bay.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
https://goo.gl/maps/LVbpSps2Bpm&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
I swam the line to the rock. Supper of spaghetti and tuna.&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;i&gt;Monday September 19&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
Woke in Nafplio before dawn. A motorboat next to us had its motor running all night. That, plus the smell of raw sewage resulted in little sleep&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
Our neighbors had put a second anchor on our boat Sunday evening, so I got ready to release their anchor when they woke. We weren't able to get it up, so we ate breakfast.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
Did yoga on the dock.&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
Motor sailed with the main to Plaka. A squall hit us just before we entered the harbor.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
We rafted with Hope's boat and Sheri's boat; our boat in the middle.&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
Bought food at 2 grocery stores, as tomorrow we will be on anchor.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
I made hor dourves: oil soaked toast, cream cheese, bacon, and local tomatoes. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
Lots of drama with incoming boats due to the gusting winds&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;i&gt;Sunday September 18&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
Woke in Nafplio before dawn. Did yoga on the dock.&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
Walked over to the beach to poop in the public toilet. Walked up the stairs 2/3 of the way up the fort. Meditated until 8am&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
Walked back to the boat for breakfast of corn flakes. I finished off the Pringles and Doritos. Had orange juice and did the dishes&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
Gene and Sandy picked up a rental van. Gene drove us to Mycenae which is a bunch of 3500 year old ruins. €12 entrance fee. Lions gate is a well preserved entrance. Next we drove 200 m down the hill to the Treasury of Atreus, an impressive tomb.&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
Lunch stop&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
Drove to Epidauras. €12 entrance fee. Another amphitheater and more ruins.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;i&gt;Saturday September 17&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
Woke in Nafplio before dawn. Did yoga and tai &amp;nbsp;chi on the dock&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
Did the dishes&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
Breakfast of corn flakes and orange juice&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
Walked up the fortress, about 860 stairs, with John. Took 45 minutes at a leisurely pace. Decided not to pay €8 entrance fee at the top. Great view of the town. Highlight of the trip so far. A group of school students were going down, and we met a few people going up and down. Did not feel crowded&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
At the base we wandered a large open air market. Clothing, fruit, and fish.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
John got free grapes. I bought dates and raisins.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
John left in search of a pool we had seen from the fort. I went to the public beach. There is exercise equipment in front of the beach.&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
I hid in the shadows to avoid sun.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
I bought two ears of corn and 2 peaches. I boiled the corn for lunch and ate the peaches while I waited. I took a nap in the boat after lunch.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
Went to dinner with sandy, pat, Teresa, and Debra. Teresa and I split a fried squid. Fresh and tender; the best I've ever had.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;i&gt;Friday September 16&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
Woke in Porto Kheli&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
Sheri was at the helm for the first hour, then I drove almost all the way to Nafplion. &amp;nbsp;Ate cold cut sandwich for lunch. Marsha was on the phone with the state department talking with the duty officer about Zonia.&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;i&gt;Thursday September 15&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
Woke in Hydra&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
Departed 9:30am&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
Motored to Vaiza.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
Swam&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
Motored to Porto Kheli, arrived 3:30pm&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
Zonia had a medical issue&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
Sandy, Pat, Debora, Teresa, and I took a small motor boat to spetsi &amp;nbsp;(€100 round trip, €20 per person). I found a cotton long sleeve shirt for €20. We walked from the new harbor to the old harbor. We walked back and had supper. I ordered Moussaka.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
Back to the sail boat by 9pm&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;i&gt;Wednesday September 14&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
Woke up in hydra before 6am on floor of cockpit&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
6 bells at 6am&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
1 bell at 6:30&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
Crazy bells at 7am&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
First boat started raising anchor 7:05&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
Wrote 14 postcards&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
Bought 7 cases of water, €2 per case. That's in addition to the original 8&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
Gyro for lunch, €2.5&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
Group dinner: fried cheese, zucchini balls, eggplant, . I ordered grilled sword fish. I helped Zonia and Cherie eat their meat (sausage, chicken, lamb, pork)&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;i&gt;Tuesday September 13&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
Woke up at 6:45 by Sandy announcing it was time to get up. Left Ermioni around 7am just in time to catch the sunrise as we motored to Hydra. Calm sea with light wind&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
Approach to Hydra was pretty.&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
Port of Hydra is small given the number of boats. Stacked 3 deep, almost all med moorings. Sandy attempted to keep our boat away from other boats in increasing wind. Lots of anchors caught on chains as people left. Sandy waited until a spot on the quay opened.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
I made scrambled eggs for a late lunch&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
I walked up the hill through the village&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
Sandy and I ate lunch around 2pm. I had a kebab gyro.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
I went swimming&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
I had a late dinner of Red Snapper with John.&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
Found a pastry shop and bought baklava&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;i&gt;Monday, September 12&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
Woke at 8am to a church bell on Poros.&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
I made breakfast of French toast. Bought ice (4 kg for €2) and milk.&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
Departed Poros around 9:30. Motored to a swim spot, Nisos Soupia. I swam to the island. Then I helped make egg salad sandwiches for lunch. I found out there are many ways to prepare the eggs (chopped rather than mashed, with onions, etc). Also, Pat and Debra were ok with shells in the egg salad!&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
Motored to Ermioni after lunch&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
Med mooring in a squall&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
6 of us ate together at a taverna. I had squid again and it was chewy&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;i&gt;Sunday, Sept 11&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
Slept on the floor of the cockpit. Good temperature and rain wasn't bothersome&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
Woke around 8am&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
Grocery store was not open, so we bought water, pastries, and coffee from a store near the marina.&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
Chocolate pastry soaked in honey was overwhelming. Spinach pastries were a hit.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
Sailed from zea marina to the coast of Aigina. I took some pictures. Then we lost wind and motor sailed to Poros&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
We rafted 3 deep off the dock; we were in the middle&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
John and I wandered the shore and walked up through a quaint village to a church on a hill. Watched the sunset over Poros.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
Walked to a restaurant recommended by a local. John ordered cod which was amazing. My fried squid was chewy. Two lessons: ask for tap water; make sure the fish is fresh rather than frozen.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
I bought rum. Made mixed drinks for John and myself.&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
I slept on the cockpit floor again and it rained again&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;i&gt;Saturday, September 10&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
Woke around 8am.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
Stretched.&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
Ate breakfast at President hotel. Spinach pastries&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
Swam in the pool on the roof&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
Taxi with John and Teresa to Zea marina at noon&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
Waited while John and Sandy got briefings&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
Went food shopping with Pat and Debra&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
Boat checkout around 5:30pm&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
Dinner at a Greek restaurant with Sandy, Pat, Debora, and Teresa. Started raining&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;i&gt;Friday September 9&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
Woke 9:38am. 15 hours of sleep!&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
Showered&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
Yoga on rooftop balcony&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
Applied sunscreen&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
Checked out&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
Walked to President hotel&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
Passed the first Olympic Stadium&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
Passed two street food vendors, a couple of convenience food stands. Lots of police standing around. Bought a ham pastry for €2.3&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
Checked in at the President hotel around 11:45am. Left my bags&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
Walked to a grocery store and bought milk, chocolate, chips&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
Bought a charger for my phone, €10&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
Returned and checked in around 1pm&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
Went swimming on the 21st floor. Outdoor pool, cold water&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
Started running into other SoS club members&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
Walked to an Indian restaurant, the Red Elephant. Ate chicken butter Masala With roti for €10.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
Slept from 9pm to midnight.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;i&gt;Wednesday September 7&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
BWI to Newark&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
Newark to Athens&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
Watched "The Lobster"&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
Dinner of yummy chicken&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
Watched "x men apocalypse"&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
Watched "the man who knew infinity"&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
Arrived in Athens around 11am on Thursday&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
Changed $180 USD to €136 @ the airport&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
Took metro for €10 from airport to Athens &amp;nbsp;(acropolis). Found my hostel and left my bags in the luggage area.&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
€30 for access to the acropolis and other attractions. Spent most of my time at the acropolis people watching&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
€1.90 for a liter of milk. Went back to the hostel and moved my bags to my dorm room&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
Withdrew €300 cash from an ATM in the metro station&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
€7.5 for ok pork meal&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
Walked over to the Olympieion&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
€1.90 for a liter of milk. More people watching&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
Free shot of ouzo on rooftop bar with great view of the acropolis&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
In bed around 6:30am&lt;/div&gt;
</content>
    <blogger:created>2017-02-04T14:50:36.024Z</blogger:created>
    <published>2017-02-04T14:52:00.002Z</published>
    <updated>2017-02-04T14:53:26.102Z</updated>
    <category scheme='tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-5921014943647686064' term='Greece'/>
    <category scheme='tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-5921014943647686064' term='2016'/>
    <category scheme='tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-5921014943647686064' term='sailing'/>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-5921014943647686064.post-2016934886247096414</id>
    <blogger:type>POST</blogger:type>
    <blogger:status>DRAFT</blogger:status>
    <author>
      <name>that one guy</name>
      <blogger:type>BLOGGER</blogger:type>
    </author>
    <title>Wisconsin, June 2017</title>
    <content type='html'>wedding</content>
    <blogger:created>2017-02-04T14:53:48.385Z</blogger:created>
    <published>2017-02-04T14:53:00.002Z</published>
    <updated>2017-02-04T14:53:58.104Z</updated>
    <category scheme='tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-5921014943647686064' term='2017'/>
    <category scheme='tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-5921014943647686064' term='wedding'/>
    <category scheme='tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-5921014943647686064' term='Wisconsin'/>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-5921014943647686064.post-3001179113806261493</id>
    <blogger:type>POST</blogger:type>
    <blogger:status>LIVE</blogger:status>
    <author>
      <name>that one guy</name>
      <blogger:type>BLOGGER</blogger:type>
    </author>
    <title>skiing in Colorado, 2017</title>
    <content type='html'>Monday: Vail. Paid $25 for parking in the garage.&lt;br /&gt;
Tuesday: Beaver Creek. My second double black diamond&lt;br /&gt;
Wednesday: Breckenridge (solo)&lt;br /&gt;
Thursday: Keystone (solo)&lt;br /&gt;
Friday&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Pro-tip: when at Beaver Creek, order the "locals burrito" at coyote bar for $5 (not listed on the menu)</content>
    <blogger:created>2017-02-04T14:55:33.514Z</blogger:created>
    <published>2017-03-03T00:24:00.001Z</published>
    <updated>2017-03-03T03:35:31.900Z</updated>
    <category scheme='tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-5921014943647686064' term='skiing'/>
    <category scheme='tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-5921014943647686064' term='2017'/>
    <category scheme='tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-5921014943647686064' term='Colorado'/>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-5921014943647686064.post-3766390965778999275</id>
    <blogger:type>POST</blogger:type>
    <blogger:status>LIVE</blogger:status>
    <author>
      <name>that one guy</name>
      <blogger:type>BLOGGER</blogger:type>
    </author>
    <title>Idaho for graduation ceremony, May 12-19 2015</title>
    <content type='html'>BWI --&amp;gt; ORD --&amp;gt; SEA --&amp;gt; Spokane, WA --&amp;gt; Moscow, ID&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Moscow, ID --&amp;gt; Spokane, WA --&amp;gt; DEN --&amp;gt; BWI</content>
    <blogger:created>2015-05-20T02:19:25.773Z</blogger:created>
    <published>2015-05-20T02:20:00.001Z</published>
    <updated>2017-02-04T14:50:02.453Z</updated>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-5921014943647686064.post-6430418792081424961</id>
    <blogger:type>POST</blogger:type>
    <blogger:status>LIVE</blogger:status>
    <author>
      <name>that one guy</name>
      <blogger:type>BLOGGER</blogger:type>
    </author>
    <title>skiing in Whistler, Canada 2017</title>
    <content type='html'>skiing in Whistler&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
BWI --&amp;gt; DEN --&amp;gt; Vancouver. Bus to Whistler&lt;br /&gt;
Bus to Vancouver, flew to ORD --&amp;gt; BWI&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
rained&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
injured my knee</content>
    <blogger:created>2017-02-04T14:54:21.233Z</blogger:created>
    <published>2017-02-04T14:54:00.002Z</published>
    <updated>2017-02-04T14:56:06.849Z</updated>
    <category scheme='tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-5921014943647686064' term='Canada'/>
    <category scheme='tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-5921014943647686064' term='2017'/>
    <category scheme='tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-5921014943647686064' term='skiing'/>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-5921014943647686064.post-7353352687261004408</id>
    <blogger:type>POST</blogger:type>
    <blogger:status>LIVE</blogger:status>
    <author>
      <name>that one guy</name>
      <blogger:type>BLOGGER</blogger:type>
    </author>
    <title>San Fransico, California 2015</title>
    <content type='html'>BWI --&amp;gt; SFO&lt;br /&gt;
Flew united from bwi at 6am eastern to noon eastern&lt;br /&gt;
Left sfo at 9:35am western time&lt;br /&gt;
Took Bart to &amp;nbsp;Embarcadero&lt;br /&gt;
walked to Ferry Building, then to pier 39&lt;br /&gt;
3pm @ Saturn's house&lt;br /&gt;
talked&lt;br /&gt;
made supper - turkey burgers with pineapple&lt;br /&gt;
Drinks with Dom at club&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Saturday&lt;br /&gt;
I woke around 7am. Made breakfast for Saturn (scrambled eggs) around 9am&lt;br /&gt;
Walked to Asta Yoga for 10am Rocket&lt;br /&gt;
Walked to Ferry Building for farmers market. Bought apple cider and apple pastry. Walked to Fisherman's wharf&lt;br /&gt;
Street car to Castro district. Hung out with Saturn and his friends @ Lookout&lt;br /&gt;
Supper at HiTop bar&lt;br /&gt;
Back to Saturns for nap at 8pm&lt;br /&gt;
Woke 11pm&lt;br /&gt;
Lyft to oasis, $6 (Saturn paid)&lt;br /&gt;
Cover &amp;nbsp;$15&lt;br /&gt;
Bought Saturn drink, $18&lt;br /&gt;
Mother's started at 1135&lt;br /&gt;
Good acts, followed by a few boring, then last was good&lt;br /&gt;
Dance until 2am&lt;br /&gt;
Taxi home, $7 (Saturn paid)&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Sunday April 12&lt;br /&gt;
Woke up 7:15am&lt;br /&gt;
Made french toast with turkey links&lt;br /&gt;
Walked to target, bought yoga mat $17&lt;br /&gt;
Bart to Asta Yoga&lt;br /&gt;
Ashtanga class with Steve&lt;br /&gt;
Bart to hertz on mason street&lt;br /&gt;
Drove over golden gate bridge&lt;br /&gt;
Parked at Sausalito ferry&lt;br /&gt;
Paid for parking to 5:50&lt;br /&gt;
Lunch at 1:40 of cod, squid, and fries for $10&lt;br /&gt;
40 minute bus ride to Muir Woods visitor &amp;nbsp;center&lt;br /&gt;
There is parking, as Stacey predicted saturday at lookout&lt;br /&gt;
Ran up and down trails&lt;br /&gt;
Back to bus stop 4:12&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
</content>
    <blogger:created>2015-05-20T02:20:34.322Z</blogger:created>
    <published>2015-05-20T02:21:00.002Z</published>
    <updated>2017-02-04T14:49:36.571Z</updated>
  </entry>
</feed>